Dr. Grant, you mentioned you have some
experience with anabolics. How would an
average person go about trying anabolics
for performance reasons? Mostly, how do
I trust the source of the actual
compounds? Let's just add a little
disclaimer that we don't promote nor
condone the usage of anab.
>> Yeah, I can't answer from a as a medical
doctor, obviously, I can't tell you how
to source anabolics. Um, but in the
past, yes, I have played with a lot of
things and you don't know what you're
getting is real. you you really take it
on faith and you hopefully use
somebody's source that you know that
they use something real but even they
don't know they just got results they
don't know that what they were taking
was what they thought they were taking.
Um, I think again this is why I'm more
on the conservative end of things and
you the one of the least faked things
would be testosterone and if guys have
never tried bumping the testosterone for
a long time low and slow that's how you
get the gains muscle these guys do
thinking I'm going to do a 10e cycle and
I'm going to get blow up with muscle.
No, you're not. It's not muscle. There's
a reason people shrivel back down. Even
professional bodybuilders, look how much
weight they lose when they get off gear.
It wasn't real muscle. It's it's not
it's water. It's inflammation. It's all
these other things going on. It's not
literal tissue. If it was literal
tissue, you would not lose that much
that quickly. And it's the same thing
when you stop a little short cycle.
Whereas somebody takes 300 milligrams a
week of testosterone with zero negatives
and works their butt off and eats right
for two, three years and might slowly
bump that dose up. You're going to be
ahead of the game on the actual muscle
tissue side of things in my opinion. Um
I mean I did crazy stupid stuff in
college and I never looked that you know
I blew up with water but I did like
1,250 milligrams a week of testosterone
with I mean it's stupid. Uh whereas
years ago, not that long ago, I did 200
a week of testosterone, 200 a week of
master for like a year. That's like
nothing. It's not even a starter cycle
for most people. Um I looked better than
I ever had at that point. Now I'm leaner
now than I ever have been. I think I
look better now than I did then and all
I'm on is my testosterone cream. But it
just time and effort, you can't replace
that. So that's just what I would say.
But as far as trusting sources, shoot,
I've been out of that world for so long
now. Like even when I was in it, I
didn't know who to trust unless you have
access to it directly. Um it was a lot
easier pre201,
you know, back in the day, back in the
good old days when uh before 911 and all
the crackdown on the borders and
everything. I mean, there was a lot of
cool stuff at that time, but I think
those days are gone.
Hey.